{"qid": "hard-agenda-0000", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/09/25 in the agenda table?", "answer": 24}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0001", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/10/11 in the agenda table?", "answer": 23}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0002", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/09/20 in the agenda table?", "answer": 27}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0003", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/03/09 in the agenda table?", "answer": 24}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0004", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/01/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": 24}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0005", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/04/27 in the agenda table?", "answer": 20}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0006", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/12/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": 29}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0007", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/12/18 in the agenda table?", "answer": 38}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0008", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/12/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": 21}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0009", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/09/11 in the agenda table?", "answer": 23}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0010", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/01/08 in the agenda table?", "answer": 26}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0011", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/11/12 in the agenda table?", "answer": 24}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0012", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/01/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": 30}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0013", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/10/11 in the agenda table?", "answer": 23}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0014", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/05/22 in the agenda table?", "answer": 18}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0015", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/01/31 in the agenda table?", "answer": 16}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0016", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/01/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": 24}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0017", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/05/30 in the agenda table?", "answer": 33}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0018", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/07/15 in the agenda table?", "answer": 27}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0019", "question": "How many events happen on 2022/05/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": 21}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0020", "question": "How many people are unavailble between 1:00 PM and 3:00 PM on 2022/06/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": 6}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0021", "question": "How many people are between 9:00 AM and 1:00 PM on 2022/10/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": 7}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0022", "question": "How many people are between 12:00 PM and 3:00 PM on 2022/03/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": 6}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0023", "question": "How many people are between 9:00 AM and 3:00 PM on 2022/06/20 in the agenda table?", "answer": 14}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0024", "question": "How many people are between 8:00 PM and 9:00 PM on 2022/09/15 in the agenda table?", "answer": 8}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0025", "question": "How many people are between 3:00 PM and 4:00 PM on 2022/01/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": 3}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0026", "question": "How many people are between 6:30 PM and 8:00 PM on 2022/02/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": 7}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0027", "question": "How many people are between 8:00 PM and 10:00 PM on 2022/06/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": 7}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0028", "question": "How many people are between 10:00 AM and 12:00 PM on 2022/06/23 in the agenda table?", "answer": 7}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0029", "question": "How many people are between 2:00 PM and 4:00 PM on 2022/03/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": 10}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0030", "question": "How many people are between 3:00 PM and 4:30 PM on 2022/06/21 in the agenda table?", "answer": 10}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0031", "question": "How many people are between 12:00 PM and 2:00 PM on 2022/09/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": 11}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0032", "question": "How many people are between 3:00 PM and 4:00 PM on 2022/05/27 in the agenda table?", "answer": 4}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0033", "question": "How many people are between 6:00 AM and 8:00 AM on 2022/12/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": 1}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0034", "question": "How many people are between 8:00 AM and 12:00 PM on 2022/12/26 in the agenda table?", "answer": 9}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0035", "question": "How many people are between 2:30 PM and 3:30 PM on 2022/04/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": 9}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0036", "question": "How many people are between 6:00 AM and 12:00 PM on 2022/08/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": 7}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0037", "question": "How many people are between 7:00 PM and 9:00 PM on 2022/10/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": 9}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0038", "question": "How many people are between 6:00 PM and 8:00 PM on 2022/09/21 in the agenda table?", "answer": 6}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0039", "question": "How many people are between 9:00 AM and 2:00 PM on 2022/06/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": 15}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0040", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Alice from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/06 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-1:00 PM, 3:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0041", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Victoria from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/08/05 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0042", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Faith from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/04/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-8:00 PM, 10:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0043", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Patrick from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/07/26 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0044", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Alice from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/03/09 in the agenda table?", "answer": "11:00 AM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0045", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Hector from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/12 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-9:00 PM, 11:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0046", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Georgina from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/03/20 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-7:00 AM, 10:00 AM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0047", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Lily from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/02/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-8:00 PM, 11:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0048", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Joshua from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/12/02 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-7:00 PM, 9:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0049", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Madison from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/12/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0050", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with James from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/04/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 4:00 PM-7:30 PM, 10:30 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0051", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Daisy from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/03 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-1:30 PM, 2:30 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0052", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Lucy from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/09 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-11:00 AM, 12:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0053", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Millie from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-10:00 AM, 1:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0054", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Layla from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/11/26 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-2:00 PM, 5:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0055", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Amelia from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/10/18 in the agenda table?", "answer": "1:00 PM-6:00 PM, 8:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0056", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Elizabeth from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-10:00 AM, 4:00 PM-8:00 PM, 10:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0057", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Emma from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/06/14 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:30 PM, 7:30 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0058", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Hector from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/01/01 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-6:30 PM, 8:30 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0059", "question": "When should I schedule a meeting with Jessica from 9:00 AM to 6:00 PM on 2022/11/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": "9:00 AM-7:00 PM, 9:00 PM-6:00 PM"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0060", "question": "What events does Brian have on 2022/03/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art walk, Book signing"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0061", "question": "What events does Benjamin have on 2022/06/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Join a fitness bootcamp"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0062", "question": "What events does James have on 2022/11/13 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Food Festival"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0063", "question": "What events does Amelia have on 2022/09/18 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Yoga and meditation"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0064", "question": "What events does Stephen have on 2022/05/22 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Employee team building event"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0065", "question": "What events does George have on 2022/07/03 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art Auction"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0066", "question": "What events does Phoebe have on 2022/12/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Cheese + Wine festival"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0067", "question": "What events does Millie have on 2022/12/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Theatre play"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0068", "question": "What events does Andrew have on 2022/06/12 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Artisanal candy making class"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0069", "question": "What events does Jade have on 2022/01/25 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Kids concert"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0070", "question": "What events does Sophia have on 2022/03/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Hiking trail"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0071", "question": "What events does Elsie have on 2022/04/17 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Casino night"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0072", "question": "What events does Imogen have on 2022/02/04 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Food festival"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0073", "question": "What events does Lily have on 2022/04/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Dinner with friends"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0074", "question": "What events does Daniel have on 2022/01/23 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Boxing class, Street art tour"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0075", "question": "What events does David have on 2022/05/28 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Art Exhibition"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0076", "question": "What events does James have on 2022/10/23 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Mindfulness meditation class"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0077", "question": "What events does Jasmine have on 2022/05/10 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Vegan Food Festival"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0078", "question": "What events does Summer have on 2022/04/07 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Book club meeting"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0079", "question": "What events does Emily have on 2022/09/19 in the agenda table?", "answer": "Theatre performance, Art Walk"}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0080", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Hannah scheduled?", "answer": 76}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0081", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Alexander scheduled?", "answer": 73}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0082", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Sophie scheduled?", "answer": 83}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0083", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Harper scheduled?", "answer": 94}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0084", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Chloe scheduled?", "answer": 88}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0085", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Florence scheduled?", "answer": 69}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0086", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Henry scheduled?", "answer": 95}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0087", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Charles scheduled?", "answer": 78}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0088", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Ella scheduled?", "answer": 85}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0089", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Andrew scheduled?", "answer": 88}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0090", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Faith scheduled?", "answer": 85}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0091", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Elsie scheduled?", "answer": 83}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0092", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Summer scheduled?", "answer": 70}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0093", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Hector scheduled?", "answer": 92}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0094", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Layla scheduled?", "answer": 74}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0095", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Jade scheduled?", "answer": 76}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0096", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Hannah scheduled?", "answer": 76}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0097", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Jasmine scheduled?", "answer": 86}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0098", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Christopher scheduled?", "answer": 86}
{"qid": "hard-agenda-0099", "question": "How many dates in the agenda table have Imogen scheduled?", "answer": 88}
